Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers, 1931-2014 MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Teaching, 267150
  - Myers, George: Introduction to Modern Times, [1982]; 270292 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "The Only Correspondence School" Letter, 1999; 270293 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Performance Artists Talking Introduction by Angelika Festa, August 1997; 270294 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Parkes, Michael Titus, 1999; 270295 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Pe.A.Ch: Performance Art Church, undated; 270296 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Perov, Kira: "California Video: A Historical Perspective", undated; 270297 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Photographic Material, undated; 270049 (Binder K)
    Binder K includes: "Fan Photos"
  - Photographic Material, undated; 271489 (Binder L)
    Binder L includes: "Student Photos"
  - Pugliese, Keith: "Linda Montano as 'Liminal': A Lifelike Artist in Performance", December 18, 1984; 270298 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Raven, Arlene: "Lives of the Saints" in Village Voice, November 19, 1991; 270299 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Reigns, Steven, 2007; 270300 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Reilly, Kara: "Linda Montano, Performance Art's Giggling Saint", undated; 270301 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Rey, Dominique, 2011; 270302 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes, Michelle: "Performance Art as Therapy Practice", June 24, 1987; 270303 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Rice, Karen Gonzalez: "Linda Montano and the Tensions of Monasticism", 2010; 270304 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Robertson, Jean: "Earth, Air, Fire, Water: A Performance by Linda Montano", April 7, 1988; 270305 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Rodriguez, Venae M., undated; 270306 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Roth, Moira: "Linda Montano Seven Years of Living Art", undated; 270307 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Roth, Moira: "Toward a History of California Performance: Part One", undated; 270308 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Shank, Theodore: "Linda Montano's Autobiographical Performance", undated; 270309 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Silver, Cai, undated; 270310 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Spaventa, Louisa, May 1998; 270311 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Stanton, Victoria: Profile, September 2004; 270312 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Straayer, Chris: "Deviant Eyes/Deviant Bodies: Sexual Re-orientations in Film and Video", September 19, 1994; 270313 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Student Autobiographies, 1995, undated; 270314 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Students in the Press, 1992, undated; 270315 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Tamblyn, Christine: "No More Nice Girls", undated; 270316 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Teaching Performance: UT Austin, 1993, 1996, 1997; 270317 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Teaching Proposal: 1986, S.F., 270318 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Tenure, Career Binder [1 of 3], 1991-1995, undated; 270319 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Tenure, Career Binder [2 of 3], 1991-1996; 270320 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Tenure, Career Binder [3 of 3], 1996-1998; 270321 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Tenure: Chris Graham Performance Correspondence: David Deming, 1994-1996; 270322 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Tenure: Complaints, Comments, Responses: Performance Art Classes, 1992, 1997, undated; 270323 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Tenure: Dean Deming Statements, 1998; 270324 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Tenure: Executive Committee Comments from Linda Montano Private File, 1992-1996; 270325 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Tenure: George W. Bush Correspondence, 1998-1999; 270326 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Tenure: Letters and Statement to Grievance Committee, 1994, 1997-1999; 270327 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Tenure: Letters of Recommendation at UT: Austin, 1996; 270328 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Tenure: Letters of Recommendation to Teach at UT: Austin, 1991; 270329 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Tenure: Letters of Support [1 of 2], 1997-1999; 270330 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Tenure: Letters of Support [2 of 2], 1997-1999; 270331 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Tenure: Letters of Support, Statements re: Sex in the Performance Classroom, 1991-1997; 270332 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Tenure: Linda Montano Merit Evaluations and Annual Reports, 1991-1999; 270333 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Tenure: Linda Montano Resume, 1998; 270334 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Tenure: Newspaper Articles: Sex Bias for Professors, 1998-1999; 270335 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Tenure Notebook, 1997, undated; 270336 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Tenure: Performance Art Class Statements and Notes, 1996-1997; 270337 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Tenure: Precedence for Performance in Class, 1982, undated; 270338 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Tenure: Support from UT: Austin Teaching Assistants, 1998; 270339 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Tenure: Unemployment Statements, 1998; 270340 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Tenure: UT: Austin Information, 1995-1998; 270341 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Term Papers [1 of 2], 1979-2007; 270342 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Includes papers by: Damali Abrams, Karen Hughes, Marla Drewinko, Jefferson Lykins, Mary Hutchison, Rose Suan Meacham, Jenni Sorkin.
  - Term Papers [2 of 2], 1986-2008; 270343 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Includes papers by: Kristine Stiles, Karen Rice, Sarah Epp, Lalena Fisher, S. Alton Dulaney, Keith Isen, Emily Kuenstler, and Joshua Fischer.
  - Unidentified Writing by Others, undated; 270344 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas Daily Planner, 1997-1998; 270345 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [1 of 8], 1991; 270346 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [2 of 8], 1992; 270347 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [3 of 8], 1993; 270348 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [4 of 8], 1994; 270349 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [5 of 8], 1995; 270350 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [6 of 8], 1996; 270351 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [7 of 8], 1997; 270352 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - UT Austin Course Instructor Surveys [8 of 8], 1998; 270353 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - UT: Austin Watchdog and Staff Directory, 1993-1996; 270354 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Whitfield, Tony: "Dressing Up Acting Out", undated; 270355 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Willey, Bob, undated; 270356 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Wood, Susan, undated; 270357 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Works by Fans [1 of 2], 2007, 2008, undated; 270358 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Works by Fans [2 of 2], 2013; 270359 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Series V: Family and Juvenilia, 267151
  This series consists of documents, photographic materials, and artworks that relate to Montano's childhood, adolescence, and family. It includes diaries, certificates, scrapbooks, and materials related to family members and Montano's time spent at a convent between 1960 and 1962.
  - Bachelor and Master of Fine Arts Diplomas, 1965, 1969; 270366 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - The Book of Baby Mine, [1942]; 270367 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Certificates, undated; 270368 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Church of Saint Mary Program, 1950; 270369 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Programs, 1959, 1965, 1966; 270370 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - "Congratulations" Baby Book, [1942]; 270371 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Convent Correspondence [1 of 2], 1960-1962; 270372 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Convent Correspondence [2 of 2], 1960-1962; 270373 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Convent: MaryKnoll Sisters: Mollie Rogers' Worldwide View, 2012; 270374 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Convent Registry and Photo, undated; 270375 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Convent Tokens, 1960-1962; 270376 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dad Album 1, 1933-1971; 270377 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Dad Album 2, 1939-1988; 270378 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Dad: Budgets, Taxes, 1950-1980; 270379 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Dad: Care Log, 2002-2003; 270380 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Dad: Health Diary, 1999-2001; 270381 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Dad: Health Notebook, undated; 270382 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Dad: Henry Montano Remembrance Book, 2004; 270383 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Dad: Illness and Death, 2002-2004; 270384 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Dad/Mom Sketches and Prose, undated; 270385 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Diary, 1986-1992; 270386 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Diary, undated; 270387 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Diary: with Quotations from the Writings of The Mother, 1983; 270388 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Dream Diary, undated; 270389 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Elementary and High School Diplomas, 1955, 1959; 270390 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Europe and College: Correspondence, 1966, undated; 270391 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Event IDs and Wristbands, undated; 270392 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - First Holy Communion Remembrance, May 8, 1948; 270393 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Her Silence Speaks by Reverend John S. Middleton, 1941; 270394 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Herman Comic Clippings, undated; 270395 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - High School and College Writings, undated; 270396 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - High School Ephemera, 1930, 1933, 1988; 270397 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Italy Correspondence, 1966, undated; 270398 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Italy Diary, 1966; 270399 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Dad, 1966, undated; 270400 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Mom, 1952, undated; 270401 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Madison, Wisconsin Correspondence, 1961-1962; 270402 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Messale festivo dei Fedeli, March 1966; 270403 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Mildred K. Montano (by Henry Montano), June 20, 1988; 270404 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Mildred Montano: The 5 Johns of John Street (Mildred's Death) Bound Final Draft, 1990; 270405 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Mildred Montano: The 5 Johns of John Street Draft, undated; 270406 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Mildred Montano Certificate of Death, June 1988; 270407 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Mildred Montano: Letter from Linda to Mildred, July 1988; 270408 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Mildred Montano: Letters of Condolence, 1988; 270409 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Mildred Montano: Mill's Last Days Drafts, undated; 270410 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Mildred Montano: Mildred's Death Draft, undated; 270411 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Mildred Montano: Tribute Book and Obituaries, 1988; 270412 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Mini Agenda Book, 1966; 270413 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [1 of 8], 1955, undated; 270414 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [2 of 8], 1961-1965; 270415 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [3 of 8], 1970-1979; 270416 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [4 of 8], 1980-1989; 270417 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [5 of 8], 1990-1999; 270418 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [6 of 8], 2000-2011; 270419 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [7 of 8], undated; 270420 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Montano Family Correspondence [8 of 8], undated; 270421 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Montano Shoe Store: Celebrating A Century of Service, March 7, 2007; 270422 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Montano Family Calendars, 1999; 270423 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Music Books, undated; 270424 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - "My Sunday Missal" and "My Lenten Missal", undated; 270425 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Religion, undated; 270466 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Photo and Membership IDs; passports, undated; 270467 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Photographic Material, undated; 270050 (Binder M)
    Binder M includes: Family Album 1, Family Album 2, Family Album 3
  - Photographic Material, undated; 271490 (Binder N)
    Binder N includes: "Convent," 1960-1962 "Montano Family Photos"
  - Photographic Material, undated; 270051 (Binder O)
    Binder O includes: "Montano Family Photos," continued
  - Photographic Material, undated; 271491 (Binder P)
    Binder P includes: "Montano Family Photos," continued
  - Two small family photo albums, 278490 (Box 94)
  - Pope John Paul II Marriage Blessing, September 19, 1987; 270468 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Prayer Cards, 1985-1986, undated; 270469 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Quarterly, College of New Rochelle, 1944; 270470 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Religious Certificates, undated; 270471 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Report Cards, Grades, undated; 270472 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Sawyer: Saugerties High School Yearbook, 1929; 270473 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - The Sawyer: Saugerties High School Yearbook, 1957; 270474 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - The Sawyer: Saugerties High School Yearbook, 1958; 270475 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - The Sawyer: Saugerties High School Yearbook, 1959; 270476 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Sketchbook / Diary, 1955, [1976]; 270477 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Special Events and Miracles in Real Time, 1981-1986; 270478 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Villa Schifanoia Graduate School of Fine Arts Catalog, 1969-1970; 270479 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Commercially Released Media, 267722
  Conditions Governing Access
  Commercially released media copies are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  All commercially released media is arranged into 3 subseries: audio, video, and vinyl. Within subseries, media is arranged chronologically by year of release. All undated material can be found at the end of each subseries.
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings, 269263
    Subseries A is arranged chronologically, where dates were designated.
    - "Have You Ever Had a Religious Experience Hour - New Music" Linda Montano, 1980; 271388 (Box 57)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: empty 1/4" audiocassette case.
      Currently available.
    - "Shri Ramamurti - Meditation on the Heart", 1980; 271402 (Box 57)
      Original format: 1/4" audiocassette.
    - "Shri Ramamurti: Mantras & Hymns to the Devi from Devi Mahatmyam", 1982; 270484 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Ramamurti & Students: Atmabodha - 'Self Knowledge' - Chanting - with Violin", 1982; 271401 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Ramamurti & Students: Healing Through YOGA SUTRAS", 1982; 270483; 3 media elements (Box 57)
    - "The Wanderer" Pauline Oliveros, 1982; 269287 (Box 57)
      Original format: 1 sound disc; digital.
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati 'Ocean of Healing'", 1985; 270487 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati & Students: Hymns to the Divine Mother", 1986; 270488 (Box 57)
    - "Sounding / Way" Guy Klucevsek / Pauline Oliveros, 1986; 271387 (Box 57)
    - "We Must All Be Explorers" Ellen Zweig and John Di Stefano, 1986; 269270 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati 'Hymns to the Guru'", 1987; 270489 (Box 57)
    - "Tara's Room: Two Meditations on Transition and Change" Pauline Oliveros, 1987; 269271 (Box 57)
    - Being Peace: Improvised Music, 1988; 269264 (Box 57)
    - "'I-AM' Mandukya Upanishad - Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati", 1988; 270490 (Box 57)
    - "Seldom Still" Brenda Hutchinson, 1989; 269274 (Box 57)
    - "Women's Mysteries: Woman of Darkness" Ione, Linda Montano, Pauline Oliveros, 1989; 269269 (Box 57)
    - "Women's Mysteries: Woman of the Lotus" Ione, Linda Montano, Pauline Oliveros, 1990; 269275 (Box 57)
    - "Women's Mysteries: Woman of Passion" Ione, Linda Montano, Pauline Oliveros, 1990; 269272 (Box 57)
    - "Svetasvatara Upanishad: 'The Book of I Am' Tape: 1", July 1991; 271396; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Svetasvatara Upanishad: 'The Book of I-Am' Tape: 2", July 1991; 271397; 2 Linear Feet (Box 57)
    - "Svetasvatara Upanishad: 'The Book of I-Am' Tape: 3", July 1991; 271398; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Svetasvatara Upanishad: 'The Book of I-Am' Tape: 4", July 1991; 271399; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Bhaja Govindam: The Song of I-AM by Skankaracharya", October 1991; 271400; 4 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Guru-Purnima Celebration with Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati Homa, Meditation, Gurustotram: 1-8", 1991; 271403 (Box 57)
    - The Hafler Trio: Masturbatorium, 1991; 269286 (Box 57)
    - "Upadesa Saram I #1-9", July 1992; 271407 (Box 57)
    - "Upadesa Saram II #17-27", July 1992; 271408 (Box 57)
    - "Satsanga - Shri Brahmananda - Yoga, Yogi & Meditation", October 1992; 271406 (Box 57)
    - "Seven Chakras" Linda Montano & The Good Sound Band, 1992; 269276; 4 media elements (Box 57)
    - Chris 'n Dave: The Basement Tapes, 1993; 269273 (Box 57)
    - "Self-Healing via Music & Incarnation of 'I AM' in You - Shri Brahmananda & Ashram Devotees", 1993; 271404; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Who Am I?" Linda Montano, June 12, 1994; 269277; 4 media elements (Box 57)
    - "Suspended Music: Deep Listening Band and the Long String Instrument", November 12, 1994; 269290 (Box 57)
    - "Deep Listening Sanctuary" Deep Listening Band, 1994; 271386 (Box 57)
    - "Tosca Salad" Deep Listening Band, 1995; 269291 (Box 57)
    - "Blue" Michael Parkes, 1996; 269283 (Box 57)
    - "Music for Enhanced Pianos" Janis Mattox and Loren Rush, 1997; 269289 (Box 57)
    - "Lesbian American Composers", 1998; 269288; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - "In the Arms of Reynols" Pauline Oliveros, May 2000; 269293 (Box 57)
    - "Charity" Michael Titus Parkes, August 2, 2000; 271384 (Box 57)
    - "SPIEL himmelerde", June 15, 2003; 269294 (Box 57)
    - "Dreamsound: Music from the Event for Sleeping Audience" by R.I.P. Hayman, 2000; 269282 (Box 57)
    - "Accordion and Voice" Pauline Oliveros, 2006; 269292 (Box 57)
    - "Extra Quality Care, 2007" Elise R Glick, 269280 (Box 57)
    - "Love Art Lab" Annie Sprinkle, Elizabeth Stephens, Guttersaint, 2008; 269285; 4 media elements (Box 57)
    - "C. Ryder Cooley: Selected Songs", undated; 269281 (Box 57)
    - Close Radio, undated; 269279 (Box 57)
    - "Hanumana Calisa: Indian Chanting 90min A", undated; 271394 (Box 57)
    - "Hanuman Chalisa: Indian Chanting A C-90", undated; 271395 (Box 57)
    - "Loop Mill about Me", undated; 271389 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati & Group: Mantras Fr. Devi Mahatmyam for Psychosomatic Healing, III: Successes in Business, Victory in Court...", undated; 271392 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati & Students: Isavasyopanisad: A Story of Awareness & Pure Consciousness of Absolute God 'I Am'", undated; 271391 (Box 57)
    - "Shri Brahmananda Sarasvati & Students: Mantras for Various Types of Healing and for Success in Business", undated; 271390 (Box 57)
  - Subseries B: Video recordings, 269265
    - Bad Attitude, 1987; 271427 (Box 57)
      Original format: VHS.
    - Rites of Passion: Volume II of the Star Director Series, 1987; 271419 (Box 57)
    - Linda Les & Annie: The First Female-to-Male Transsexual Love Story, 1992; 271429 (Box 57)
    - The Sluts and Goddesses, 1992; 269266; 2 media elements (Box 57)
    - Woodstock Summer of '94: Not the Music Just the Scene, 1995; 271428 (Box 57)
    - The History of the Future, 1998; 271412 (Box 57)
      Original format: CD-ROM.
    - An Intimate Guide to Female Genital Massage, 1999; 271430 (Box 57)
    - Annie Sprinkle's Herstory of Porn, 1999; 271420 (Box 57)
    - "Shifting Positions", 1999; 271422 (Box 57)
    - Zen Pussy: A Meditation on Eleven Vulvas, 1999; 271426 (Box 57)
    - Tehching Hsieh: One Year Performance, 2000; 271413 (Box 57)
      Original format: DVD-ROM.
    - "Transgenic Hairshirt", 2001; 271421 (Box 57)
    - Red Wedding #1, December 18, 2004; 271411 (Box 57)
      Original format: DVD.
    - School Board Blues: A Docu-Memoir, 2004; 271415 (Box 57)
      Original format: DVD-R.
    - Annie Sprinkle's Amazing World of Orgasm, 2007; 271425 (Box 57)
    - Stanley's House, 2007; 271417 (Box 57)
    - Freedom from Dental Fears, 2009; 271418 (Box 57)
    - "Walking with Linda Montano" Damali Adams, 2009; 271410 (Box 57)
      Original format: DVD+R.
    - The Catskill Mountain House and The World Around, 2010; 271416 (Box 57)
    - Cecil Taylor & Pauline Oliveros: Solo Duo Poetry, 2012; 271414 (Box 57)
    - Sweet Violets, 2012; 271424 (Box 57)
    - Cancer: Just a Word... Not a Sentence, undated; 271423 (Box 57)
    - "Unforgiving Art? Unforgivable Nation?" Video Program 18 min, undated; 271409 (Box 57)
  - Subseries C: Vinyl sound discs, 269267
    - "Music for the Fireside" Paul Weston, 1950; 271236 (Box 58)
      Original format: 1 vinyl sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - "Music for Lovers Only" Jackie Gleason, 1952; 271256 (Box 58)
    - "Soft and Sweet" The Three Suns, 1955; 271234 (Box 58)
    - "Symphonie Fantastique" Charles Munch, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1955; 271240 (Box 58)
    - "Festum Mariae Assumptae" Saint Joseph's Abbey Choir, 1957; 271260 (Box 58)
    - "Mu Sigma Epsilon presents Eleventh Annual Choral Clinic Concert", March 21, 1959; 269296 (Box 58)
    - "Listen to the Quiet..." Joe Bushkin, 1959; 271235 (Box 58)
    - "Japanese Language Record Course" Conversa-phone Institute, 1961; 271233 (Box 58)
    - "The World of Miriam Makeba" Miriam Makeba, 1963; 271242 (Box 58)
    - "Ella at Juan-Les Pins" Ella Fitzgerald, 1964; 271257 (Box 58)
    - "El Nuevo Estilo de La Guarachera" Celia Cruz, 1965; 271239 (Box 58)
    - "Folksongs of Eastern Europe" The Pennywhistlers, 1965; 271076 (Box 58)
    - "Celebrations For a Grey Day" Mimi & Richard Farina, 1965; 271241 (Box 58)
    - "Ab Main Ne Man Dekhe" Khansahib Abdul Karim Khan, 1966; 271066 (Box 58)
    - "The Brazilian Sound Restrained Excitement" The Zimbo Trio, 1967; 271230 (Box 58)
    - "Folk Songs of Old Eire" Judy Mayhan with Dulcimer, 1967; 271253 (Box 58)
    - "Three Ragas" Ravi Shankar, 1967; 271245 (Box 58)
    - "Silk Purse" Linda Ronstadt, 1970; 271246 (Box 58)
    - "Don't Cry Now" Linda Ronstadt, 1973; 271243 (Box 58)
    - "Different Drum" Linda Ronstadt, 1974; 271259 (Box 58)
    - "Heart Like a Wheel" Linda Ronstadt, 1974; 271264 (Box 58)
    - "Modern Scream" Lily Tomlin, 1975; 271068 (Box 58)
    - "Pieces of the Sky" Emmylou Harris, 1975; 271237 (Box 58)
    - "Prisoner in Disguise" Linda Ronstadt, 1975; 271248 (Box 58)
    - "Hasten Down the Wind" Linda Ronstadt, 1976; 271261 (Box 58)
    - "Simple Dreams" Linda Ronstadt, 1977; 271263 (Box 58)
    - "Classic Alberta Hunter" Alberta Hunter, 1978; 271252 (Box 58)
      Format: 1 vinyl sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - "I Can't Stand It" Beth Anderson, 1980; 269268 (Box 58)
      Original format: 1 vinyl sound disc: analog, 45 rpm; 7 in.
    - "Mad Love" Linda Ronstadt, 1980; 271073 (Box 58)
    - "Get Closer" Linda Ronstadt, 1982; 271069 (Box 58)
    - "Accordion and Voice" Pauline Oliveros, 1983; 271071 (Box 58)
    - "Artists Doing Songs" High Performance Issue #23, 1983; 271247 (Box 58)
    - "The Wanderer" Pauline Oliveros, 1984; 269295 (Box 58)
    - "Anitra's Dance" Oslo Philharmonic Orchestra, undated; 271064 (Box 58)
    - "Armenian Love Songs" Onnig Dinkjian, undated; 271231 (Box 58)
    - "Ave Maria" West India Company, undated; 271258 (Box 58)
    - "Bach" The Philadelphia Orchestra, undated; 271238 (Box 58)
    - "Dhyanam/Meditation: South Indian Vocal Music" K. V. Narayanaswamy, undated; 271250 (Box 58)
    - "Folklore D'Abruzzo", undated; 271063 (Box 58)
    - "Guru Gita" Muktanda, undated; 271262 (Box 58)
    - "The Hare Krishna Mantra" Swami Bhaktivedanta and His Disciples, undated; 271065 (Box 58)
    - "Holst: The Planets" Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra, undated; 271244 (Box 58)
    - "Istanbul: Authentic Music of the Near East", undated; 271074 (Box 58)
    - "Magnolia: The Voice of Lutfi Guneri in His Latest Hits" Lufti Guneri, undated; 271249 (Box 58)
    - "Meditation / Introduction to Self-Analysis" International Center for Self-Analysis, undated; 271232 (Box 58)
    - "Plays for Dancing" Erroll Garner, undated; 271265 (Box 58)
    - "The Radha" Krsna Temple, undated; 271251 (Box 58)
    - "Rosenkavalier Waltzes - Part 1" Richard Strauss, undated; 271067 (Box 58)
    - "The Songs of Milarepa" Mahayana Buddhist Nunnery, undated; 271254 (Box 58)
    - "Songs of a Russian Gypsy" Theodore Bikel, undated; 271255 (Box 57)
    - "S-U-N Meditation and Self-Analysis" International Center for Self-Analysis, undated; 271075 (Box 57)
    - "Tony Makes It Happen!" Tony Bennett, undated; 271070 (Box 57)
    - "Yoga Exercises and Relaxation Techniques" International Center for Self-Analysis, undated; 271072 (Box 57)
- Series VII: Non-commercially Released Media, 267152